campusnet.net 2004-12-08

# Campus Management Corp: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Campus Management Corp. respects your privacy and is committed to protecting any personal information that you provide to us. Our goal is to deliver content that will be useful to you. In order to provide relevant information, be responsive to your specific requests, and enhance your experience while utilizing our website, we will from time to time request information from you. 

This statement explains our policies and practices regarding the use and disclosure by Campus Management Corp. of the personal information you provide. It is important for you to understand that Campus Management Corp. reviews and updates this Privacy Policy as it deems appropriate without notice to you. As a result, you should periodically review this policy to make sure that you are aware of how we are using the personal information you provide us. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Campus Management Corp. as explained below. 

Campus Management Corp. provides links to other sites we believe may be of interest to you. These sites are provided as a convenience and are beyond our control and Campus Management Corp. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content on these web sites. You should check the privacy policies of those sites before providing your personal information to them. 

Copyright & Trademarks

Campus Management Corp. and the Campus Management logo are trademarks or registered trademarks of Campus Management Corp. Other trademarks or registered trademarks of Campus Management include CampusVue, Campus2000 and Design, CampusNet (stylized), CLASS Software (stylized), CampusLink (stylized) and CampusCare (word mark). 

All other trade names are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective holders.

Copyright © Campus Management Corp 2004. All rights reserved.

Collection of Information

In general, you can visit our web site without providing us with any personal information. However, at various times during navigation across our web site, there are instances where we need your personal information to grant you access to our protected and secured sites. This information may include registration data, such as your name, address, email address and phone number. Campus Management Corp. may collect information from you through the use of user request forms to send you information you have specifically requested from us. Campus Management Corp. may also request information that will assist you in better using Campus Management Corp. products and services. This information may include information about your organization and your responsibilities within that organization. Please do not submit any personal information to us if you are less than 18 years of age. 

Use of Information

We may use the information provided by you for various purposes to enhance your business relationship with Campus Management Corp., including: engaging in transactions or communications with you and your employer; verifying compliance with the agreement between Campus Management Corp. and your employer; providing future service and support; responding to user inquiries and requests for information; and informing you of new product and service offerings as they become available. 

Disclosure of Information

Although Campus Management Corp. does not sell, trade or transfer your information to third parties; we may share the information with our business associates for various reasons, including marketing, advertising or product and service offering purposes. We would also disclose this information if we are required to disclose it by court order or other legal process. 

Security

The accuracy and security of your personal information is important to Campus Management Corp. If you contact us to make any changes to your information, we will attempt to make those changes in a timely manner. Campus Management Corp. is concerned with the security of your information and has in place reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized access to that information. To that end, we put in place the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to secure your personal information. 

Usernames and Passwords

Access to certain content on our web site may be allowed under a written agreement between you or your employer and Campus Management Corp. and will require a username and/or password. In some cases, failure to provide personal information may prevent you from accessing certain parts of our web site that may contain certain confidential information. 

General

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, please contact Dr. Jack Elcik [jelcik@campusmgmt.com](mailto:jelcik@campusmgmt.com).
